isunshare.com 2019-08-27

# iSunshare Privacy Policy - Protect Your Personal Information

Your [Privacy](https://www.isunshare.com/privacy.html) is a priority at iSunshare. We go to great lengths to protect it. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.

## Why we collect personal information?

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

## How do we collect the information?

There are numbers of different ways that iSunshare receives and collects personal information from you. Ways iSunshare collects personal information from you may include the following:  
**Communications**  
When you email or write to us you may need to provide us with your name, contact details, and other personal information in your message.  
**Support**  
You may need to provide us with personal information when you telephone or email us to request technical assistance in respect of our products, or to request information that you would like to receive relating to our products.  
**Registration**  
Upon registration of one iSunshare product you will be asked to provide certain information which we will use to record you as an owner of the iSunshare product and to assist us in providing you with service and information.  
**Purchases**  
If you wish to purchase iSunshare products from our Store, we will require sufficient information to complete your purchase including your credit card details and your contact details.

## How we protect your personal information?

iSunshare uses secure server hosted by Swreg, RegNow and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt the entire customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number and credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

## About Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a little text file composed of alphanumeric characters, which is created on your computer when your browser accesses a website that uses cookies. The files are used to help your browser navigate the website and fully use all its features like logins, preferences, language settings, themes, among other common features. The cookie is used solely to help your browser process a website, it doesn't collect any information from your computer or snoop on your files, and they cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.
